<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="about.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="special.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="information.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="secure.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="time.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cookies.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="more.xsl"?>
<database>
    <section>
        <about>
            The Digital Maths Academy switches kids on to maths. It is engaging, supportive
            and targeted for Kids aged under 12. Students across Ireland and in further
            development will target kids worldwide, aligned for a huge variety of international
            curricula. We love to celebrate our greatest Mathletes! Will you or your school
            make it onto our leaderboard of top scorers? Complete your Quiz work and earn
            points for your daily total. Digital Maths Academy gives each student its very own
            peesonal workspace. Filleds quiz mathamatical quizzes to test you Math logic.
            Digital Maths Academy caters for the evolving learning styles.
        </about>
    </section>
    <section>
        <special>
            Ask your parent or guardian for permission before you send any personal
            information over the Internet, including to our Web Sites. Digital Maths Academy
            has no intention of seeking personal information about minors who visit our Web
            Sites. If such information is collected, this Privacy Statement will apply to that
            information. In addition, if we can identify a user as a minor, the personal
            information will not be used for further marketing and promotion unless the
            minors guardian has consented. We encourage you to ask your children to seek
            your permission before providing information about themselves or their family
            over the Internet.
        </special>
    </section>
    <section>
        <information>
            To send a confirmation notice to the Registrant of the registration. 
            To respond to any questions, concerns or problems raised by the Registrant. 
            To send out a Digital Maths Academy Learning newsletter or emails about the
            Site. 
            To publish the names of winners and high performers on the Site or in the
            Digital Maths Academy newsletter and to provide all the results data for each Registrant.
            To send leaderboard results for participation and performance on the Site.
        </information>
    </section>
    <section>
        <secure>
            Digital Maths Academy is committed to information security. We will use all
            reasonable endeavours to keep Registrants personal information in a secure
            environment. For instance, each Registrants personal information is encrypted
            whilst being sent to our server at the time of registration. However, security
            cannot be guaranteed due to the nature of the internet. Digital Maths Academy
            security measures are designed to assist in Registrants personal information not
            being accessed by unauthorised personnel, lost or misused. If you reasonably 
            believe that there has been an unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal
            information please let us know by contacting our Privacy and Data Protection
            Officer (contact details below).
        </secure>
    </section>
    <section>
        <time>
            We will keep any personal information we collect from Registrants for as long as
            they are registered users of the Site. If a Registrant cancels their registration or it
            otherwise lapses after 3 years of not using the Site, we will only keep their
            personal information for the purposes of sending the Registrant information
            regarding Digital Maths Academys learning other products and services if they
            agree to receive this information. Personal information is otherwise deleted or
            destroyed.
        </time>
    </section>
    <section>
        <cookies>
            A cookie is a little piece of information handed to a web browser from a web
            server that contains information that can be retrieved from the server later. When
            you visit the Site the server may attach a cookie to your computers memory.
            Digital Maths Academy uses cookies only to the limited extent to recognise the
            Registrant when they visit the Site and pairing that Registrant with the account
            (and account preferences) that the Registrant created. However, this information
            is not linked to any personal information that Registrant may provide and cannot
            be used to identify Registrants. You should be able to configure your computer so
            that it disables cookies. To help us better understand you needs and better share
            content, we also use analytical software. This software will save a cookie to your
            computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage
            of the website but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can
            read Google's privacy policy here for further information. Other cookies may
            be stored to your computers hard drive when this website uses referral programs,
            sponsored links or adverts which is extremely rare. Such cookies typically
            expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is
            stored, saved or collected without your consent.
        </cookies>
    </section>
    <section>
        <more>
            Get in touch with our friendly team of educational specialists at The Digital Maths
            Academy Contact Page. We want to hear from you. We will always respond to
            questions within 24 Hours! Garenteed.
        </more>
    </section>
</database>